It's really really hot today, we're going
to make super simple Biscoff ice cream.
Biscoff is sometimes called Lotus
biscuits in some parts of the world,
other parts of the world it's called
Biscoff, call it what you like,
you know what it is. We're going to use the
Ninja creami so let's just get on with it...
You're going to need cream between 30 and 35%
fat, milk doesn't make any difference what fat
percentage, you're going to need a can of
condensed milk 300 ml that gives you 350g
and then your Biscoff Spread. So we're
going to weigh out our cream we're going
to need 286g of cream like that, we're
going to need 218g of our milk like that,
we are going to need the entire can of condensed
milk like that, make sure to lick the [Music]
spoon.... yummy and then
into that we are going to add
156g of
spread 156g, what's this..... this is 380g so
a tiny bit more
there we go delicious. No stabilizers,
its super high fat we put these away
[Music]
if you want to use a stabilizer thing too but as
it's so high fat we generally don't need it stir
this together really well the Biscoff is going
to fight you because you know putting it into
cold liquid it's going to go slightly harder
but just keep stirring and then eventually
you can just check that it's all done nice
that is our base into our creamy tubs it
goes with that in there Lids on into the freezers
however long it takes to freeze 5 hours [Music]
later all right this one took a while to freeze
cuz it's pretty hot high fat but um it's going
to be worth it [Music] the the caramel notes that
come with using condensed milk really benefit this
recipe and that's why I'm using it again but next
week we're going to go to much more complex ninja
creamy recipes more in line with what you'd
expect from this channel I I'm doing these
fast ones to show that you can create good ice
cream really quickly but let's get this one spun
[Music]
up right as you can see it's got a really nice
color and and let's get some scooped up into our
Bowl delicious looking ice cream super
super smooth Biscoff crunchy ice cream
in your Ninja creamy couple of things to point out
before we try the fat percentage of
this recipe is relatively high but
that's where good ice cream comes from that's a
joke by the way to balance this recipe you have
to look at the ingredients you have to look at
the fat percentage and sugar percentage of your
spread and this will stand for anything that you
use in your ice cream you need to understand what
you're putting in it and because of that I needed
to balance it out with more milk otherwise it's
just too much fat when I balance this recipe
it started up at 24% fat way way too high
so balancing that back down with the milk
the sugar and the solids from the condensed
milk and obviously the the whipping
cream at 33% you can use 35% that's
fine will create this super decadent
fudgy Biscoff ice cream let's dive in
yes bloody hell starting to uh surprise all
the ninja cream is starting to surprise me
somewhat Ultra smooth not a speck of ice in it
bis cof has got this kind of um cinnamony kind
of undertone to it there's no cinnamon in
there and there's no cinnamon I don't think
in the cookies themselves oh no there is
well there you go and that's why I taste
cinnamon I mean look look at how
creamy that
is so good I know you can get this stuff
pretty much anywhere the only thing I
will say is that spinning it in the creamy
you've lost all of the crunchy Parts which
is a shame because the crunchy Parts actually
really good but it has made it very smooth
so all the crunchiness is gone no major hardship
anyway I'm going to play with my mustache finish
off the last little bit of this ice cream
thanks so much for watching don't forget to
like And subscribe next week we're going to do
a complex ninja creamy recipe I'm going to do my
best to try and get these out during the week
midweek sometimes I just can't du to life um
but hey if you don't want to miss out on the video
make sure you like subscribe and click
that notification Bell see you next week
[Music]